Prophecy Time
There is a brother that just came back from the prison yard.
The key thing is that your wife was the one who reported you
and immediately they deported you.
He is under the gallery.
Prophecy Time
I am the person the man of God prophesied about, who has been to prison
and was reported by his wife.
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers prayer and deliverance to people
from across the world in the name of Jesus Christ.
As he prays for Mr Sioni, the evil spirit responsible for his recent calamity is arrested
and confesses its crimes.
Who are you?
Family idol.
What have you done to him?
Fornication.
What else?
Pornography.
Debt.
Deportation.
You deported him from where?
From America.
What happened that he was deported?
He abused a child.
Failure.
What have you done to his marriage?
No marriage.
How did you enter him?
Idol.
After the confession of the evil spirit for the world to hear and learn,
Prophet T.B. Joshua delivers Mr. Sioni from every hidden spirit
threatening his peace, his success and his future.
As he falls to the ground, the wicked spirit is cast out forever.
Thank You, Lord! I'm delivered!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
People of God, Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Sioni Ayodeji Fanugbami
I am from Ondo State (Nigeria).
I was a resident in the U.S. before coming back to Nigeria.
First of all, I want to apologise to the man of God
because I used to be one of those people who really didn't believe in this ministry and the man of God,
following the bandwagon of disinformation because people used to say that
he buries some cows somewhere here,
he uses snake power,
he sleeps with some of his staff,
he consults the devil.
So I believed all that.
But I never knew that he was the one who would end up being my deliverer.
I want to apologise and ask for forgiveness;
ask God for forgiveness for castigating the man of God.
The problem that brought me here - as the prophet said - was prison.
In 2006, I left the country on U.S. visa lottery.
Ok. Before you left the country, sir, could you tell us a little bit more about the kind of family you are from,
and what happened that you left the country for America.
I came from a very poor background.
My people were still in Ondo State.
They even still do not fancy me coming here.
But there is nothing that anybody can do; this is my place of salvation.
Through me, all of them will come here eventually.
This is a part of my testimony - my life story.
I came from a very poor background.
I was struggling before I left.
I was working at a printing press in Lagos before I left.
It was during that time in 2005 that I applied for the visa lottery.
I was selected, went through the process and then travelled out.
My family background - I was born a Muslim.
On my father's side they are Muslims; on my mother's side they are Christians.
In the middle we have the family idols and all that.
I have really been exposed to all kinds of horrible elements
like eating at the shrine, going with masquerades,
a lot of bad dreams - dreaming of snakes, cows chasing me, people shooting at me.
So it has really been tough but in 2006 I left the country for the USA.
When I got there in 2006, I was supposed to be serious with God.
But I was never serious with God; I was living the American dream in the wrong way.
I began drinking alcohol.
As someone who had never been drinking before travelling out,
I began drinking when I got to the U.S.
The level of alcohol I was drinking -
you would expect someone who had never been drinking to start small.
But I started with the strongest alcohol you could find there
like the fire-in-your-bones alcohol so that when I drank it, I passed out.
I would not know where I was until the next day when I opened my eyes.
All these things continued.
At a point, when I was at university, I dated seven different ladies.
None of them knew each other.
I would schedule one for the morning, I would schedule one for the afternoon,
I would schedule one for the evening and schedule one for the night.
I was really out there.
I began smoking and going to clubs.
So at that point, you were in a relationship with seven different women at the same time,
and none of them knew that you were with another woman?
None of them knew.
I kept on going like that.
I lost focus.
Eventually I even had to drop out of university - biochemistry with a focus on premedicine.
I had to drop out eventually.
It was one the ladies that I had been with for three years that called the police on me
because one of the nights that I was at her house -
I was already drunk, we were both drunk, I was wasted -
by the time I opened my eyes in the morning, I was in the child's bedroom.
So the problem was already there and the child told the mother that I was trying to rape her.
We just want to understand clearly what happened in this scenario.
You said you were completely drunk
and when you woke up, you were in the bedroom of a young child -
the child of that lady.
And that is how you woke up in that scenario?
Yes, I was extremely drunk, we were both drunk - I and the child's mum.
When I woke up---
Like I said, when I drank, I wouldn't know what happened because of the alcohol I took.
If you google the kind of alcohol I took, it can drive a car.
That was what I was drinking.
And tequila is very strong.
And brandy is very strong.
So I would blend tequila and brandy; I would spice it with a little bit of orange juice.
That is what I would drink.
I would be lost.
Even one of my girlfriends said---
There was a night that I was with her - this is another lady.
After I woke up in morning, she said she was scared because she thought I was dead
because I was just laying in bed like I wasn't breathing, my chest wasn't moving.
So that is the way I would drink.
I would drink and then just lose consciousness.
This is precisely what happened with this lady that night.
When I woke up in the morning, that is when I realised, "Oh, why did I end up in here?"
And then the little child told her mother that I was trying to rape her.
She called the police; I couldn't reconcile with her.
I was arrested.
I was put into detention for three months, got bonded out and then I began going to trial.
It was when I now began going to trial in 2013 that I met a man of God
whose ministry is a partner with Emmanuel TV in the U.S.
He was the one who introduced me to this ministry.
At first when he told me, I was like, "What in the world are you doing with T.B. Joshua?
You could have gone to a better place where they've got real fire,
where they preach real gospel".
I never knew that T.B. Joshua was the one who would end up delivering me.
Even though I came from the same region, the same state where the prophet is from,
I never truly believed in him.
That was how I got to know Emmanuel TV.
So it was an American pastor in the USA
who was actually the one who told you about Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Even though you are a Nigerian and from the same state, you never believed in him.
It was this encouragement from an American pastor that opened your eyes
to discover Emmanuel TV and know Prophet T.B. Joshua - the truth about him.
Absolutely.
I was even trying to discourage him from talking about it or playing the videos.
I was like, "This man ain't real. Go to other places where they preach real gospel".
Eventually I started listening. I was like, "I must listen to what this man is all about".
Even though I had known about him before I left the country
but because of disinformation, I didn't want to have anything to do with him.
Eventually I began listening to the prophet, and I began praying with him.
And then hope started coming to me.
Even though I was already going through trial -
in fact, I was looking at 30 to 40 years in prison for the sentence.
When I began praying with the prophet, hope began coming.
When I lost the case and they gave me simple battery, I was shocked,
"Oh my God! Without a paid lawyer and you got a public defender!
And you got a simple battery over a case as significant as this!"
I was grateful and then they gave me a five-year sentence in 2014.
By the special grace of God, they let me out after two years.
When they let me out, I came here and I have been coming since I got back this year.
Ok. So a sentence that you were expecting to be 30 to 40 years because of the issue of rape
actually ended up being just a five-year prison sentence.
And after two years, you were released and deported back to Nigeria.
Absolutely.
When they let me out, I had to leave the country because I was not a U.S. citizen.
After I had been in the U.S. for ten years, they said I had to leave because they couldn't let me stay there.
I signed and then ended up in Nigeria.
When I came, it happened that as God loves me so much, He gave me a new beginning.
On the 7th of this month, I had a revelation and I saw the prophet giving me a note.
On that note, he wrote the number 17.
That was on the 7th of this month.
So he gave me a note with the number 17 on it but I never really understood it.
Here was the prophet giving me a note with the number 17 on it but I never really understood it.
But then when I came to church on Sunday, the 16th, he called my case.
And when I stepped out, that was it.
On the 17th that he had written down on the note was the day I got my deliverance.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Brother, can you just describe to us when you received that deliverance.
What happened to you as the prophet prayed for you?
Even before I left Nigeria, it had been one nightmare after another.
I would see cows chasing me, like I said.
I would see all kinds of strangers; some of them would be men trying to romance me.
Snakes would be biting me; people would be shooting at me.
I got shot three times in my dreams.
Masquerades were coming after me like, "You got something we need!"
They would be chasing me all around.
It was one nightmare after another - eating in the dreams and all that.
But then after I was prayed for, since Monday, I have been sleeping like a little baby.
I have no bad dreams - no woman is showing up in my dreams;
no ghost is trying to get me.
I'm grateful to God.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So that was how our brother was completely delivered.
Brother, as the prophet prayed for you, we saw that evil spirit manifesting.
Can you just recall what happened when he prayed for you?
How did you feel at that moment when he prayed for you?
When his hand hit me, it was like my brain was put into trillion different places.
And then I just lost it.
There was something telling me, "What are you doing?"
But I couldn't control it; I was no longer myself.
The power of God already took over.
In fact, the Sunday night that the prophet called me out,
I had a dream and I saw this huge guy that I had never seen before.
One of his arms was about my whole size.
The guy was so huge.
That was the Sunday night I received the prophecy.
He was telling me, "Oh, where have you been?
Because I didn't come with you to church on Sunday.
Do you think you can escape from me?"
I asked him, "Who are you? and then the dream just changed.
That was the ancestral spirit, the family idol,
the stronghold that had been impeding me all my life.
And that was how that spirit was cast out,
and ever since then your life has changed?
Yes, sir.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Brother, in the course of your testimony, you mentioned as well
that you were under the affliction of this spirit of lust, alcoholism, smoking.
Ever since that deliverance, what can you tell us about the changes in those areas?
When that crisis hit, it was like the Lord Jesus actually used that crisis
to slap me back into reality because He loves me; I believe He loves me.
I have seen Him in my revelation too.
All the urges, all the desires, all the gravings for all that are gone now.
I have peace like I have never had before in my life.
That hit me when I was delivered.
It was like somebody lifted a truck off my chest.
I felt so light.
After my deliverance I was laughing and rejoicing; I was happy.
Ever since then I have just been happy.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
We thank God for our brother's life.
Right now, sir, what is your word of advice to our viewers all over the world?
Oh man! The greatest lesson for me here is:
If God loves you, He won't take 'no' for an answer.
It is very painful to be disciplined by God, even though the end is going to be good.
But it is painful.
I really didn't have to go through all this
but this is the way I chose to learn a simple lesson.
And the lesson is: Don't ever be on the wrong side of history with God.
Believe in Him, trust in Him.
Put all of your hope on Him.
And He will definitely take you to your final destination.
Amen. Glory be to God. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Finally, sir, you said you were in the past among those who condemned Prophet T.B. Joshua,
criticised him, call him all sorts of names.
But at the end of the day, the person you thought was a devil
ended up being the same person that God used to deliver you.
What is your word of advice to people who have maybe a similar impression
or have a negative opinion towards Prophet T.B. Joshua
as a result of rumours or slanderous remarks they have heard
based on your own life experience?
Even now when I hear the prophet, it is like I have never even heard his voice before.
I can feel the love coming out of his messages.
I can feel the power coming out of his heart.
My advice to everybody out there who is sceptical is:
Please, stop begin sceptical; you are delaying yourself.
You are really holding yourself back.
It is not godly, it is not righteous to talk against a man of God.
The step of righteousness is for you to go to God and find out -
"Is this guy real? Is this guy genuine?" -
before you join folks who don't know what they are doing to be castigating a man of God.
Please, one word: Stop!
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Sioni Ayodeji Fanugbami.
I am from Ondo State, Nigeria.
I was recently deported from America.
You are welcome, brother. Can you tell us what Jesus Christ has done in your life
since you stepped your feet into The SCOAN?
It has been mind blowing; it's been amazing.
It is undescribable.
Contrary to my previous opinion about this place, I was really proven wrong.
Since I came here, the prophet has showered me with nothing but love.
They've been taking care of me.
I received my deliverance here, and I'm extremely grateful to God and to the prophet.
We thank God for your life, brother.
Now that you have received your deliverance and are ready to start life afresh with Christ Jesus,
what plans do you have now, what steps you want to take?
Actually, my number one priority in life now, in fact the only desire I have now is to do the will of God.
Even though I already have so many business plans drawn up,
I know I need wisdom to guide me where to go to from here.
My number one desire now is to do the will of God.
If I do business, it is going to be Kingdom business.
And if I do ministry, it is going to be Kingdom ministry.
Just looking for every opportunity to serve God for the rest of my days.
We thank God for your life. On a very practical note, when you were deported from America to Nigeria,
is it that you literally came with nothing?
I absolutely came with nothing.
In fact, the pants and trousers I am wearing right now are the only trousers I came down with,
with two shirts and one pair of shoes.
I have been living with my junior brother ever since I got back.
In fact, I came back from America with 280 USD.
Armed robbers came to the house and stole some of it.
The rest just went into personal upkeep.
I really have nothing, and I literally have no one to help me.
We have listened to our brother. We thank God that he has been delivered from his past life.
He has been restored by our Lord Jesus Christ, here at The SCOAN
after receiving that word of prophecy and deliverance.
Brother, we are here right now with a message for you from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The man of God said that he wants to support you in all departments of your life
as you are about to start this new journey with Christ.
Not only in your spiritual life but also materially and financially as well.
So on behalf of Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners,
we are here to present to you this cash gift of 200,000 naira as well as the Word of God.
Oh my God!
This is super amazing!
Thank You, Jesus! Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua!
This is mind blowing! This is beyond me!
In fact, my mindset for coming here was not for money because I could spend money easily.
My mindset for coming here was really to encounter the real love of God of Prophet T.B. Joshua
and I'm glad I have done so.
This is the first part of my testimony.
The second, third, fourth, fifth parts are still coming.
But I'm extremely grateful to the prophet.
I thank the Emmanuel TV partners.
I love you, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Wow, we thank God Almighty.
In addition to the 200,000 naira, we are also giving you the Word of God, 'The Mirror',
just as a reminder for you as you have rightly said.
Go out there and make the Word of God the standard for your life.
So once again, this is 200,000 naira as well as the Word of God
from Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners
for our brother to really begin his new life with Christ Jesus in a wonderful way.
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua! Thank you, Emmanuel TV partners!
Thank You, Lord Jesus, for bringing me here!
I'm grateful; I'm extremely grateful.
Thank you.
Amen. We thank God for your life once again, brother.
Finally, we'd just like to ask: Now that you have received all these wonderful blessings
from our Lord Jesus Christ, what is your word of advice and encouragement to our viewers?
Oh my God! Please, people all over the world, stop procrastinating.
Stop listening to people that are castigating the prophet.
Please find the means to come here.
Find a way to come here.
Solution is here, love is here and you can't find that in most places.
Please come here and get delivered.
Come here and meet the Lord.
Come here - the prophet is waiting for you with arms stretched out
and with nothing but love in his heart.
The Lord God Almighty is here, Heaven is already open up over here, waiting for you.
Stop procrastinating, come here right away.
The Lord is waiting for you.
Amen. We thank God for our life.
Indeed, our brother is encouraging you to seek our Lord Jesus Christ in spirit and truth
and we believe Jesus will guide everyone to a living church
where the Holy Spirit will take control of their case.
Brother, we thank God once again for your life.
We pray that God will give you the grace to continue making His Word the standard for your life,
and we are sure you are coming back with even more wonderful testimonies, in Jesus' name.
Amen.